Contact

maui_hearts@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sandy-hart-rn-cnor-46252957 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Nursing

Hospitals

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau International-Honor Society of Nursing

Sandy Hart RN CNOR

RN CNOR at AMN Healthcare

Birmingham, Alabama

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Physician Relations, and Intensive Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate's degree focused in Nursing from George C Wallace State Community College-Hanceville.

Experience

AMN Healthcare

1 year 1 month

RN CNOR

June 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Travel Nursing

RN CNOR TRAVEL NURSE

June 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Tailored Healthcare Staffing RN-CNOR

February 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

UAB Medicine

RN CNOR - GU/ROBOT 2016 - Present (4 years)

Birmingham, Alabama

University of Alabama at Birmingham RN CNOR PLASTICS/SURG ONCOLOGY/ORAL SURGERY February 2015 - 2016 (1 year)

UAB Medicine

10 years 4 months

RN CNOR GI/ENDOSCOPY TEAM LEADER

Page 1 of 2

April 2013 - February 2015 (1 year 11 months) BIRMINGHAM, AL

RN CNOR GI/SURGICAL ONCOLOGY TEAM LEADER November 2004 - April 2013 (8 years 6 months)

UAB Medicine

RN

November 2003 - 2004 (1 year)

Birmingham, Alabama

Circulate and scrub various Gynecology and Gynecological Oncology procedures

Education

Wallace State Community College Associate's degree in Nursing, Nursing · (1989 - 1991)

University of Alabama at Birmingham